DAVID BALDUS PAPERS (APAP329) 1965-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- North Carolina Research, 2008-2011; 18; 2.4
  - Offenses Incurring Death Penalty, ca. 2011 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Table 1 - White Victim Cases, ca. 2011 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - New Jersey Reference Materials, ca. 2011 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, ca. 2011 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, ca. 2011 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Qualitative Extension Analysis, Undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Reference Material - North Carolina Racial Justice Act, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Reference Material, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Preliminary Report on The Findings of the North Carolina Death Penalty, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Coding Costs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Figure 1 - with Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Appendix A - N.C. Salient Factors for Classifying Factually Comparable Cases, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - North Carolina Capital Case law Handbook, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Lexis Nexis Article - N.C. Criminal Law Procedures, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Qualitative Extension Analysis 2, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Transcript - Video Conference, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - North Carolina Capital Case Handbook, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - In Binder - Narrative Summaries in North carolina Death Penalty Study, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Reference Material - Tennessee Law Review, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Affidavit of Catherine Grosso and Barabara O' Brien, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Reference Material - State of North Carolina v Roger Mckinley Blakeney, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Data Reports - with Case Specific Data Summary, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Court Case - State of North Carolina v James Edward Jaynes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Lexis Nexis Article - State of North Carolina v John Wesley Oliver and George Moore JR, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Article - Potential Saving from Abolition of the Death Penalty in North Carolina, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Portion of Essay - Involving the Findings of Adjusted Analysis, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
- McCleskey Stories, 1987-2008; 19; 0.4
  The McCleskey Stories highlight the significance of the case McCleskey v. Kemp and the lasting impact it has on the Death Penalty in the United States.
  - In Binder - McCleskey v Kemp Law Briefs, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2006 September 20; 2006 October 24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Law Brief - McCleskey v Kemp, 2007 September 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Reference Material - Law Briefs, 2007 September 25 -28; 2007 October 1; 2001 October 15; 2007 October 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Supreme Court Opinion - McCleskey v Kemp, 2007 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Reference Material - Pre McCleskey Decisions, 2007 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - McCleskey Stories Workshop, 2008 May 16; 2008 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - McCleskey v Kemp Report, 2008 August 18; 2008 September 22 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Handwritten Edits - McCleskey v Kemp Report, ca. 2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Table 1 - Unadjusted Race of Victim and Race of Defendant Disparties, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Reference Material - Law Articles, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - In Binder - Law Briefs and Other Related Documents, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)